good morning or good afternoon or good
tag depending on when and where you are
watching this this is a product review
about beautiful skin um I know that
every product really annoyingly talks
about youthful glow but I kind of reject
that because as I get older that I have
no shame about getting older I like
getting old order actually have a little
bit more disposable income I know a
little bit better about what suits my
body I have a teeny tiny bit more wisdom
and I find life is easier to manage so I
don't see why I should hanker after
being younger because it's quite nice
where I'm at anyway so that's my Rand
basically I would like to be a 34 year
old woman woman who doesn't look
massively tired but I know that that
wouldn't really fit onto a tiny little
pot
so my son was up all last night teething
I was up and down up and down so these
are the products that I use in a
situation like that things that just
give my face a bit of a lift and make me
not look like I've slept under a bridge
my first product love is from benefit
it's called you rebel I was given this
by a friend about 3 years ago I still
got half it left it's brilliant it's
such a good value it's about £25 you can
buy all of these from boots so you can
get your boots points yes free money
um this is what you put under your
foundation or you can wear it on its own
it's just it's almost like a a pasty
creamy thing you rub it in and it just
it's the most beautiful consistency it's
not oily it's not greasy but it gives
you a nice little glow without a shimmer
now I like a glow and I like to look
healthy what I don't want is a shimmer
because I'm not 16 I don't want a
glitter y Shimmer yeah but that that is
not you can't even see cuz I'm all the
way over here but it's this is a
fantastic fantastic product especially
if you have young children and your
sleep gets interrupted that is a
lifesaver the next one I think is a
great everyday product cuz I know I've
talked about eom Foundation before but
it is quite expensive and I don't use it
everyday but this is the Smashbox camera
ready BB cream what I love about this is
It's SPF 35 so you don't need to faff
about with an underlayer of
SPF this is £
26 it's really good value again you
hardly it's quite strong coverage so you
don't need that much I quite often just
use it around this in this area when I'm
filming but it is it is brilliant and
also you don't need a toner you don't
need a primer because it's a BB cream
it's got it all in and it really does
work but it is I would say that's a
little bit too thick for me every day
this is something I've used for years
and years and I haven't yet found
anything that is better than this for an
everyday cheap foundation this is the
Max Factor ageless Elixir it's a two in
twoin one Foundation Plus serum does
make a difference because it doesn't
leave any chalky residue um I use the
light Ivory which is number 40 and it's
spf1 15 again which really helps with
the layering that is
$12.99
that I think is the best High Street
Foundation you can buy done that's all I
have got to say about that it's the boss
this is its kind of slightly crappier
little
sister if my skin is very hydrated and
there's no chance of it being chalky or
showing dry patches then I think this is
fantastic this is $1.99 and this is
again Max Factor skin
luminizer Foundation and again it's the
light Ivory that I use um this this is
they're they're pretty much the same
product but I find this is much more
moisturizing but this has a little bit
more of a glow to
it that is a great product but what I
really think the the two done products
that go hand in hand are the benefit U
Rebel and the Max Factor agis Elixir
those are what I use pretty much every
day they love last for ages so they're
incredibly good
value so to all those moms and dads cuz
these you know these work on men's skin
except you might want to Fresh shave um
for all of those parents who are up and
down all night but don't want to look
like a dog's
dinner easier guys see you
later
oh